

My name is Vincent and I work as a front-end developer. Currently I live in Stockholm, Sweden and work at the digital agency Daytona Communications.

Design and technology has always been my main interests and with both these passions web designer is the best job for me! After studying system development and computer science I've been freelancing and worked at different web agencies. Right now I'm working at one of Sweden's best digital agencies where I work with clients such as <a href="Coop">Coop</a> and Systembolaget.

When I'm not working with clients I like to "kick back" and do some side projects to keep the creativity and my code-brain going.

## VINCENT ORBACK

vorback@gmail.com | +46 725 309 222 | vincentorback.se

## **Experience**

Daytona Communications

2013 - Now Stockholm, Sweden

Front-end developer

Queensbridge

2012 - 2013 Stockholm, Sweden

Front-end developer

Traffic Light

2012

Developer (Internship)

Freelancing

2012 - 2015

Developer and designer

## **Education**

Malmö University

2011 - 2012

Computer Science System development Web development 1 Web development 2 Motion pictures

Södertörn University

2011

English A

Riddarfjärden High School

2011

Graphic design & Journalism